ここには １名しか　おらぬようだが あえて　お主達と言っておく。
Pursuit x And x Analysis
完全に把握されている 小細工は無駄
After a tip about the Phantom Troupe,
Gon and his friends move out.
お主達の「念」に触れて 強く感じたのは
There, they encounter Machi and Nobunaga.
憤怒　恐怖　憎悪ではなく
However, the two aren't just
waiting around to be caught.
使命感　覚悟の類いであった。 人類の存亡を背負っての 戦いならば
Was Uvo really killed? Probably.
もう終わった。 はっ！
Uvo was more than just a dumb brute.
そしゃくが必要か？ 耳を疑っているようだな
I know that.
ならば　何度でも言おう お主達の勝利だ　戦いは終わった。
Even if he were fighting
a difficult opponent, he had the wits and experience to prevail.
ここからは お主１人に語り掛ける。
I'm the one who submitted the request. You're late! Where are you?
ここへ　余が来た理由は 複雑ではない。
Stop looking around... I can see you.
ただ一つ。
It's the couple behind your boyfriend?
コムギという人間に会いたい それだけだ。
I'll wire the money to you now, so please confirm receipt.
他には　何も望まない。
Hurry! But Uvo didn't return.
お主の「念」に触れて 余の現状と　この先も理解した。
Has he ever been late without informing us?
それを知った上で　なお 今　余が望むのは
But remember what he said? He wasn't coming back until he
settled up with that chain user.
残された時間を コムギと過ごしたい
That's why I said probably.
それだけだ。
I never said he was definitely dead.
今のは　私の…。
We aren't strong enough to handle them.
私の性格に触れた上での 作戦かしら？
What was that? We won't know until we try! And why are you saying this now?!
いいえ　分かってる！ あり得ない！
Quiet... They'll notice us.
信じられると思う!?
But it's still true.
素直に 「あぁ　そうなの」と言えると!?
I knew it as soon as I saw them.
絶対の王が ちっぽけな私を偽るために
My dad once had a hit on a Troupe member. Huh?
自分自身を偽るなんて…
What? One of the few times I've
ever heard him complain.
あれだけの虐殺を！ そして　これからも…。
Said the job wasn't worth the price.
そんな生き物の…。 敗北宣言も　人への思いも…
That's considered the greatest
compliment a target can get.
無理!!　絶対に無理よ!!
That was when he told us
真実だからこそ　王は！
to stay away from the Troupe.
ほんの少し…　だったと思う。
It's been a few years, so I thought we might stand a chance...
えっ？
They're really that strong?
どこかで　ほんの少し 何かが　ほんの少し違っただけで
Would it help you to picture
two Hisokas sitting there?
今の余ならば 神とまでは言わぬが　この世を…。
That is definitely not something we can handle. So, why do you think they're here?
いや…　全てが一致しての 現在だからこそ
Aren't they on a date? Huh? Really?
そう思うだけなのかもしれぬ。
No, they noticed that other
couple behind them.
余に時間がないのは承知であろう。
They're paying close attention
to their surroundings.
自力で捜すより お主から聞きたいのだ。 何言ってんの!?
At first, I thought it was just caution
because the Mafia is after them.
やめて！ そうよ 私は彼女の居場所を知ってる！
But in that case, they wouldn't
be sitting in a public place.
拷問でも何でも自由にしたら？ 分かってるの！
They aren't worried at all.
それが不可能なのは お互い十分　分かっているはず。
They're waiting for someone to find them.
お主のオーラは 今まで見た中で　最も強く美しい。
Acting as bait, to draw out their prey. We're being watched.
やめてよ…
They aren't amateurs.
余にできるのは ひたすら頼むことだけだ。
Yeah, I can't tell where they are, but they're focused on us. Is it the chain user?
ダメ!!
I believe the boss wishes to recruit him. Machi...
私も　もう　一部はアリ。
Have you forgotten the unspoken rule? Alive or dead.
By any means necessary.
あなたが種にとって どれほどの存在か
Right?
嫌だけど分かってる！
You're free to interpret the
boss' orders as you like, but you can't force me to agree.
そこまで…　それほどまで…
I haven't said anything yet. You're the one forcing the issue.
それだけはダメ 言うわ。
The atmosphere changed.
だけど　１つ条件がある。
I've got a really bad feeling... Did they notice us? It's okay. They haven't noticed us yet.
私の能力で　あなたを…。
Are you sure? Besides, I can't use Zetsu like
you guys to mask my presence.
あなた達を見届けていい？
If we used Zetsu, that would
attract their attention.
是非もないこと。
They're trying to see if there's anyone
ごめんね　キルア
So you'd better wipe those
looks off your faces. Act normal.
約束　破っちゃったよ…
Sorry, that was a bad idea. Let's make it clear, then.
４－７－１　「帥」…。
I see...
フッ…　フフフ…。
It was wise to switch rooms.
起きろコムギ　打つぞ！
The Phantom Troupe is definitely
using the pro Hunter website. If you'd moved any later,
Neon might have been in danger.
[TV]　衝撃的なニュースが 入ってまいりました。
Is that okay, Neon? Well, I don't have a choice.
[TV]　東ゴルトー共和国の 全国民を集結させた 大人民大会の真の目的は
The auction was canceled,
so I don't have any reason to stay.
総帥自身による大虐殺でした。
I really wanted to go...
[TV]　ディーゴ総帥は
They'll hold another auction next year.
すでに　がれきの中から 遺体で見つかっており
Cheer up.
無理心中の公算が 大きい状況ですが
And I promise I'll recover
ナンバー２であるビゼフ長官の 所在　安否は依然不明のままで
the items you wanted from those bandits. Really? Yes, I promise.
革命の可能性のほうが 有力であると
Have I ever broken a promise?
一部の情報筋は 警戒を強めています。
Have you ever kept a promise?
[TV]　一方　ミテネ連邦のＮＧＬでも 異変は起きており
You make a good point...
亡命者の確認など 国際保安維持機構が
I believe your names are
Melody and Basho? Yes...
連絡を試みていますが
You'll take Neon back to
the house immediately.
全く応答がない状態です。 [TV]　もともと　東ゴルトーと ＮＧＬとの間には
To be on the safe side,
use simple disguises.
黒い噂が絶えず 今回の事件を契機に
Okay, Neon. Return to your room and pack. Okay.
ＮＧＬにも　機構の強制捜査の メスが入ることは必至です。
All right, let's get down to our real business.
んっ？　ああ
The auction will resume tonight.
ボスは責務を全うしたよ。
The time and location haven't changed.
いや　俺は直接見ちゃいねえ。
The community must demonstrate
そこが　ちょっとばかし微妙でな。
that they will not allow anyone
to intimidate them.
ああ　パーム待ちだ。
The Ten Dons have vowed to
recover the stolen merchandise.
[TEL] いいんですか？　王の生死確認を たった１名に任せて。 [TEL]　しかも　その人 一度は敵側に捕らえられて
The stolen merchandise? As I told you earlier, the man we captured claimed
吸収されてるんでしょ？
that a Shadow Beast had taken
everything before they arrived.
[TEL]　まぁ　そこは プロ意識のせめぎ合い。
Yes, that's correct.
[TEL]　万全を期した上で 完璧な報告をするのは 確かに　プロさ。
The Shadow Beasts appear to be wiped out.
[TEL]　でも　それは 空調完備の部屋で
Nine bodies have been recovered so far.
椅子に座ってる奴のプロ意識だ。
The final member, Owl, was the one
[TEL]　俺達　現場は　信じた仲間が 任せろと言ったら任せるのさ。
carrying the merchandise. He was probably captured by the Troupe.
どっちもプロだ！ ただ　俺は現場だ！ 事務じゃ　ねえ！
The Ten Dons understand how
frightening Nen can be.
ん…。 副会長派には通用しませんよ その理屈。
If the Troupe has someone who can
use Nen to compel confession, they wouldn't even need torture.
バレたら　聴聞は 最低　覚悟してくださいよ。
It's believed that the merchandise Owl took has fallen into the Troupe's hands.
[ﾊﾟｿｺﾝ]　あ　えっと　ワシ　ネテロ。
Considering our opponents, it would be better to leave it to the experts.
会長　お疲れさまでした
crush the Troupe for us,
while avoiding further losses.
ゆっくり お休みになってください
However, it's also a chance to make a
name for ourselves in the community.
同日　ネテロがハンター協会の 会長職を辞する旨と
We cannot allow those hit men all the glory.
後任人事についての メッセージが記録された動画が 電脳サイトで配信され 話題となったが
So, Kurapika... I want you to join those hit men.
それが遺言であると理解した者は ごくごく　わずかであった
Take care of the chain user for me. Got it.
さぁ　乾杯しよう。
They're on the move.
What should we do?
乾杯しようじゃないか 人というものどもに。
As I told you, we can't
beat them in a fight.
善人も悪人も　いつの世も
We'll find a way... We have to. Yeah.
人は　くり返す。
We can't leave empty-handed. Okay.
膿むには余りに長く
Then listen carefully.
学ぶには余りに短い　時の螺旋上。
Gon and I will tail them. We absolutely cannot let them spot us.
だからこそ　好く欲し
We'll use Zetsu.
好く発するのだろう？
Wow...
命など　陽と地と詩とで
I can see him standing here,
but I can't sense him. Gon, I need you to make me two promises.
満たされるほどのものなのに。
If they see us, we give up
immediately and escape.
終わったわ。
The signal to stop will be one phone call. Make sure your phone's on vibrate.
いや　ものすごく 久すぶりな気がするす。
Yeah, I was on his tail for a whole day.
夢で打つのと やっぱり本物は違いますねや。
Wow, not bad. Ow... Why did you hit me?
うむ。
Uh, it seemed appropriate.
突然　お腹ば　すごい勢いで 蹴られだ感ずがすて
Well, then you should have no problem.
その後　気付いだら 変な人に　さらわれで。
Be sure to stay out of
their field of vision. Okay, let's go. Yeah!
余ではない　余の配下だ。 ぶはっ　んですたか！
The targets have passed the plaza
and entered a side street.
ワダすったら早とちりをば。
Okay, confirmed.
余には過ぎた者達だ。
Do they know we're here? It's okay. We're using Zetsu, so they shouldn't notice
us unless something's really wrong.
んだらば いらっしゃいますたら　お礼をば。
But they're on constant guard
against pursuers, so stay vigilant.
余から伝えておこう。
Yeah. You, too.
じきに会う。
Tsk, he's telling me to be careful?
はい！
It's okay.
以前　余の名を聞いたな。 あ…　はい。
They haven't noticed us. When they realize we're here,
they'll react in some way.
余の名は　メルエムだ。 )
They can try to conceal it, but their faces or behavior will betray it.
)
I've been put through life-or-death
shadowing exercises since I was three.
メル…　エム様。 あっ！
I won't fail and lose sight of them!
ワ…　ワダすの名前はコムギです！
Are we being followed?
どうぞ よろすくお願いいたすます！ 知っておる。
Most likely, I'd guess.
いや…。
I'm impressed.
そうだな　知らなかった
I can't sense a thing.
余は　何が大事なものかを
They must be quite skilled.
い…　いや めっそうもございません。 総帥様を呼び捨てなど 絶対にできません！
Crap, they're moving toward a deserted area.
ならば　軍儀で余が勝ったら
They must realize by now that
they're being followed.
お主は余を　「様」抜きで呼べ。
Then is this a trap?
分かりますた。 えと　呼び捨ての後で 死んだらいいですか？
No, they don't know our exact locations. Or maybe they don't know they're being
followed and are heading back to base.
あぁ　そうだったな。
That would make this a huge success. Is this a trap?
死ぬ必要はない。
Or their hideout?
以前の余とは　ひと味　違うぞ。
If it's a trap, we should run immediately.
幾多の敗北を覚悟しておけ。 はい！
If it's their hideout, we should continue.
愚問か
Our stalker isn't taking the bait.
では　行くぞ。
It probably isn't the chain user.
１－５－１　「帥」。
I can sense multiple people tailing us.
９－９－１　「帥」。
But the chain user works alone.
７－９－１　「兵」。
How can you be sure? He's a member of the
Nostrade Family, right?
２－３－１　「兵」。 ２－７－２　「筒」。
Yet he managed to defeat Uvo on his own.
まさか
I'm sure because the Mafia
hasn't taken any action.
７－１－２　「砦」。 これは… 「孤孤狸固」！
If the Mafia were responsible, they would use Uvo as a chip
against us, dead or alive.
コムギ　余を愚弄するか？
Had they killed him, the news would
probably be on the Net by now.
いいえ。 心して答えよ。 戯言には付き合わぬぞ。 はい。
Since there's nothing, the chain user probably defeated Uvo alone, without reporting it to the Mafia.
ワダす 軍儀で　ふざけたことないです。 分かった　貴様
Why would someone who works
for the Mafia operate solo?
負けたら　やはり死ね！
It was probably a personal grudge.
はい。
You're using "probably" a lot. Shut up.
死路ではないと申すか
would team up with anyone else.
余の検討でも いくつか路はあった
Thus, the chain user is operating alone
だが　それは全て いたずらに手を増やすだけで
and unrelated to the group now pursuing us.
勝ち目の薄い近死路ばかり
Your theory has a lot of holes.
活路があると申すならば…
Then what do you think? Indeed...
９－２－１　「中将新」！
I suspect that there's a link between
this tail and the chain user.
この先
You just know?
見せてみよ！
I just know. Man...
４－６－２　「忍」！
One or the other. Do they know we're following them?
こ…　これは！
Right now, it's fifty-fifty. But they don't know our location. They want to draw us out because
they don't know where we are.
確かに
They may be waiting for someone else.
路が生きた！
Hold your position and wait.
あの夜　気付いてすまったんです。
Gon, I'm hanging up.
黙れ！
Pay close attention.
考えさせろ！
If they give any kind of reaction,
we'll run for it!
ここだ！　ここしかない！
Phinks here. Oh, what's up? I wanted to see how you were doing.
詰め切れぬはず！ 相手が無理に寄せれば
We're being followed,
but they haven't made a move.
手を重ねるほど　こちらが有利！
And we can't locate them,
so this will take a while.
かといって早めに攻撃を緩め 攻め手を　こちらに譲れば
Oh, then would you like some helpful info?
「騎馬」と「中将」の中押しを 防ぐ手はあるまい！
Hmm? What do you mean?
やはり言わねばならぬな。
He stopped me with ease... With one hand!
メルエム様。
Yo.
最期を コムギ…
Phinks, why are you here?
お主と打って過ごしたかった。
Weren't you heading out with the boss?
だが　この毒は伝染する。
This is the fourth floor. To fool the enemy,
you first fool your allies.
余のそばに長くいれば
The boss got me good again.
お主にも…。
I wondered why there were so
many Zetsu masters around.
逆新手…　返し!?
They fooled us! Okay, kid.
メルエム様。
I have a few questions for you.
とっても幸せです。
Boy, do you know the chain user?
ふつつか者ですが お供させてください。
Huh? A Nen user who uses chains to fight. We're looking for him.
そうか　余は…
He asked you to follow us, right? I don't know who that is.
ワダすは　きっと
We were following you
for our own reasons. I just need one moment...
この日のために生まれて来ますた。
With an opening, I can escape! Well?
この瞬間のために 生まれて来たのだ
Well, indeed... If he's lying, he's really good. I can check.
４－４－１　「兵」。 ６－５－１　「騎馬」。
Boy, your friend surrendered.
２－７－２　「忍新」。
I'll ask you once more. Do you know the chain user?
コムギ　いるか？
My answer is the same.
はいな　いますとも！ どこにも行きません。
I don't. I see. How about you?
４－５－１　「中将」。
Any guesses?
お前に一度も勝てなかったな。
Welcome to our base.
何をおっしゃいますやら 勝負は　これからですよ！ そうだな。
They stand inside the
Phantom Troupe's hideout...
１－５－１　「帥」。 ９－５－１　「帥」。
...nerves mounting to their limits.
名前を… 呼んでくれないか？
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia Brush Your Teeth.
Unripe Fruit
おやすみなさい。
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia Today, we introduce Machi. A Phantom Troupe member. A Phantom Troupe member. She's a Transmuter.
メルエム。 ワダすも　すぐ　いきますから。
Transmutes aura into Nen
threads that she controls. She can turn her aura into Nen threads. Her special technique is Nen Stitches. She can put your body back together! Like this!